Contact

9010994117 (Home) manjunathvustepalli@gmail.c om

www.linkedin.com/in/vmanjunath98 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

JavaScript
React Native
angular

Certifications

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

Front End Libraries

Javascript tutorial course

v manjunath

looking for opportunities

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Summary

Experienced Application Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in HTML,CSS and JavaScript,bootstrap and frameworks like angular,react native. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Engineering focused in Information Technology from B N M Institute of Technology, BANGALORE.

Experience

MAP Systems
Application Developer
March 2020 - Present (3 months)
Bengaluru, Karnataka

Centura Technologies Application Developer November 2019 - March 2020 (5 months) Bangalore

Hindustan Aeronautics Limited Intern July 2018 - August 2018 (2 months) Bangalore

Developed a website on die tracking which is used currently at hal.

Education

B N M Institute of Technology, BANGALORE
Bachelor of Engineering, Information Technology (2015 - 2019)

Narayana Junior College - India 12 · (2013 - 2015) Montessori High School - India 10 · (2003 - 2013)